<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Road Trip America</string>
    <string name="title_activity_car_list">CarListActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="destination">Destination</string>
    <string name="garage">Garage</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>

    <!-- Text Strings for Garage Fragment -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_car">NewCar</string>
    <string name="test_text">2011 Ford Taurus FWD</string>
    <string name="car_pic">Picture of user\'s car.</string>
    <string name="test_city_mpg">City MPG: 18</string>
    <string name="test_hwy_mpg">Highway MPG: 27</string>
    <string name="edit_car_button">Edit Car Button</string>
    <string name="view_specs">Edit</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">

    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="editCarYear">YEAR</string>
    <string name="editCarMake">MAKE</string>
    <string name="editCarModel">MODEL</string>
    <string name="editCarType">TYPE</string>
    <string name="remove_vehicle"><u>Remove Vehicle</u></string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

    <string name="car_icon_license">Sports Car by Linus Knappe from the Noun Project</string>
    <string name="about_the_app">Mission: To provide the best travel experience across America\’s open highways.\n\nAbout: We here at Road Trip America are dedicated to help you plan your trips across the United States by providing relevant information on the way to and at your destination.We currently offer approximate fuel cost to reach a destination based on the car you drive and current average fuel prices.\n\nVehicle Information: All vehicle information is gathered by feuleconomy.gov and MPG data is based off of EPA estimates. MPG can vary greatly depending on how and where you drive, vehicle condition and maintenance, fuel variations, vehicle variations, and engine break-in.\n\nFuel Price Information: The price of fuel is obtain from the U.S. Energy Information Administration and will be updated along with application updates the second and fourth Tuesday of every month.\n\nDisclaimer: All fuel cost, MPG data, and distance to a destination are estimated.</string>
    <string name="upcoming_features">This section provides details of features coming with the next application update.\n\n1.) Will have the option of selecting a starting point, not just current location.\n\n2.) Will be able to select route options i.e. avoid tolls, avoid highways, etc.</string>
    <string name="licenses_agreements">Road Nature Forest Trees Photo provided by Harrison Faux\nhttps://www.pexels.com/photo/road-nature-forest-trees-45775/\n\nSports Car by Linus Knappe from the Noun Project\nhttps://thenounproject.com/term/sports-car/1391902/</string>
    <string name="epa_notices">EPA has issued a Notice of Violation to Fiat Chrysler Automobiles N.V. and FCA US LLC for Model Year 2014 to 2016 light duty diesel vehicles (Ram 1500 and Jeep Grand Cherokee). All relevant data from the affected vehicles has been removed from this website until further information is available.\n\nIn 2016, the Department of Justice alleged violations of the Clean Air Act by Volkswagen (including Audi and Porsche) covering all of Volkswagen\'s 2.0L and 3.0L diesel vehicles sold in the United States since model year 2009. All relevant data from the affected vehicles have been removed from this website until there is an EPA-approved emissions modification.</string>
    <string name="privacy">As of this release, no information of your activity is being stored or shared with a 3rd party. The app only uses your location to obtain directions and the number of miles to a destination for in app fuel cost calculations only. Your location is not being updated in the background and future releases of this app will allow for location services to be turned off.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">AboutActivity</string>
</resources>
